sitetalkmall.com 2010-12-29

# SiteTalk Mall - Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy 

We presume that if you visit/use our websites, you have read the following Privacy Policy and have understood the content. By remaining on our sites that you accept our Privacy Policy, if not, please leave our websites now.    
These websites are hosted from SITETALK Communities Ltd Suit B.29 Hearley Street London W1 G 9QR UK. SITETALK undertakes everything possible to maintain that the information are protected on the highest level. Every decision made from any individual on the basis of information contained in our websites is exclusively the responsibility of the individual himself. SITETALK cannot guarantee that the content at all times is applicable due to the continuous changes being made. 

#### Collection of Your Personal Information

In order to register as a participant of our community, you will be required at all times to sign in with user name and password. You will be able to access the different SITETALK sites using the same username and password. By signing in through one SITETALK website, you may be automatically signed into other SITETALK sites. As part of this registration process, you may also be requested to provide questions and secret answers, which we use to help verify your identity and assist in resetting your password etc.   
We ask you when registering to provide personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address or telephone number. We may also collect demographic information, such as your postcode, age, gender etc. If you choose to make a purchase over the SITETALK Web Shop, we may ask for additional information, such as your credit card number and billing address, which is used to create an SITETALK billing account.  
We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with SITETALK. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every Website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.  
When you receive newsletters or promotional e-mails from SITETALK, customised links or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click, in order to provide you with more focused e-mail communications or other information in the future.  
In order to offer you a more consistent and personalised experience in your interactions with SITETALK, information collected through one SITETALK Website may be combined with information obtained through other SITETALK -participants-Websites

#### Sharing of Your Personal Information

Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside SITETALK and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent.  
We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on SITETALK; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of SITETALK (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of SITETALK websites or participants of the public. (d) the completion of all necessities concerning your contractual relationship with us..  

#### Use and transfer of Your Personal Information

SITETALK collects and uses your personal information to operate and improve its sites and carry out the transactions you have requested. This with regard to the information you have send to us e.G. for the purchase of products in the SITETALK-shop or concerning those information you have send to other participants and therefore legible by everybody.   
We also use your personal information to communicate with you. We may send certain mandatory communications such as welcome letters, billing reminders and information on technical issues.   
Personal information collected on the SITETALK sites may be stored, processed and transferred in the UK or any other countries inside or outside the European Community in which SITETALK or its affiliates, subsidiaries or agents maintain facilities. SITETALK guarantees that the transfer of private information to other affiliates will comply with this Privacy Policy and SITETALK guarantees the highest level of data protection.  
By using any SITETALK site you consent to any such transfer of information outside your country. You explicitly agree with the transfer of personal information like name, home-address and e-mail-address to Unaico Ltd,1508 Concordia Plaza,Tsim Sha Tsui East Hong Kong for the reason of sales promotion if you haven’t already contradicted in writing.

#### Cookies

SITETALK websites use "cookies" to enable you to register as a participant of our SNP Website and to help personalise your participant ship online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer.  
SITETALK Websites use cookies to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to enter the same information repeatedly and to display your personalised content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these sites.

When you sign in to a site using your username and password, the SITETALK system stores your unique username, and the time you signed in at, in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from page to page on the site without having to sign in again on each page. When you sign out, these cookies are deleted from your computer. The system also uses cookies to improve the sign in experience. For example, your e-mail address may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your e-mail address to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. If you are using a public computer or do not otherwise want this information to be stored, you can select the appropriate radio button on the sign-in page, and this cookie will not be used.  
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of the SITETALK websites.

#### Changes to This Privacy Statement

We will occasionally update this privacy statement to reflect changes in our websites and participant feedback. When we post changes to this Statement, we will email all participants. If there are material changes to this statement or in how SITETALK will use your personal information, we will notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes prior to implementing the change or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this statement periodically to be informed of how SITETALK is protecting your information.
